<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MarvelInfinite</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>

    <string name="stanbio">Stan Lee left behind a massive legacy.
He was the creative leader of Marvel Comics, and along with some co-creators such as Jack Kirby and Steve Ditko, he created a universe of heroes that would become well known around the globe. In the 1990’s, he retired from his role in the company, shortly before his comics began developing into movies. However, his retire did not stop his influence, as he then became a public figurehead and a permanent “Executive Producer” position on every film thereafter.
Today, he is widely known as the creator of the Marvel Universes, and he even makes a cameo appearance in every single movie.
Though he passed on November 12, 2018, he will forever be respected in every community he was a part of.
Excelsior!
</string>

    <string name="soul_bio">
        The Soul Stone is the most mysterious Infinity Stone. Its first appearance was in Avengers: Infinity War. Thanos
        acquired it by travelling to Voromir and sacrificing Gamora, his adopted daughter. The stone is guarded by the spirit
        of Red Skull. According to the Russo Brothers, this Red Skull Spirit has no memory of his previous life, but is rather
        an entirely new entity. Despite all this, no one is quite sure exactly what it is the Soul Stone actually does.
    </string>
    <string name="time_bio">
        The Time Stone is the most green Infinity Stone. While its powers are not completely clear, it has the ability to
        alter time. It was wielded by the character Doctor Strange in the movie Doctor Strange. In Avengers: Infinity War, Strange was forced to give the stone to Thanos. The extent of
        its powers that was shown is present in Doctor Strange, where Strange puts himself in a time loop during his confrontation with Dormamu.
        It is also able to rewind time in a certain limited space. In Wakanda, Scarlett was forced to destroy the Mind Stone, and therefore destroy her
        beloved Vision. Thanos used the Time Stone to revive Vision, only to kill him again by ripping the Mind Stone out of his head.
    </string>
    <string name="mind_bio">
        The Mind Stone is perhaps the most impactful stone, emotion-wise. It was the final stone acquired by Thanos. It originally
        came from the God Scepter of Loki. In Avengers: Age of Ultron, the Avengers captured the Scepter and Tony Stark and Bruce Banner started
        studying it. Stark allowed J.A.R.V.I.S. to experimenting with it. It eventually became the driving force behind Vision and Ultron.
        In Avengers: Infinity War, Thanos ripped the stone out of Vision's head, effectively killing him and emotionally tearing Scarlett Witch
        apart. It has the ability to control people\'s minds.
    </string>
    <string name="space_bio">
        The Space Stone was the second Infinity Stone in Loki\'s arsenal during the attack on New York in The Avengers. This stone presided in the Tesseract.
        The Tesseract has a long history, but eventually was found by Nick Fury in Captain Marvel, where it then stayed in SHIELD headquarters. Loki
        then took it and used it to open holes in space for his Chitaurian army. The Space Stone has the simplest ability: it can let the user travel through space. Loki actually later
        stole the Tesseract from a falling Asguard in Thor: Ragnorok.
    </string>
    <string name="power_bio">
        The Power Stone is the most powerful out of all the Infinity Stones. It\'s ability is giving immense brute power to the user.
        It was used by Ronan in his attack on Xandar in Guardians of the Galaxy. After Ronan was defeated by the Guardians, the stone was under the
        protection of the Nova Corps. Unfortunately, Thanos would then attack Xandar again (not in a movie) and acquire the Power Stone. This was
        the first Infinity Stone that Thanos added to his gauntlet.
    </string>
    <string name="reality_bio">
        The Reality Stone is one of the more interesting Infinity Stones. The Reality Stone took the form of the Aether in Thor: The Dark World. However,
        its true power was not revealed. Later, it was stored in the Collector\'s museum in Knowhere. In Avengers: Infinity War, Thanos travelled to
        Knowhere and attacked The Collector. There, it was revealed that the Reality Stone can literally alter reality. As Thanos stated, "Reality
        can be whatever I want."
    </string>
</resources>
